rupeetalk.com 2010-05-29

# Home Loans,Credit Cards,Personal Loans,Life Insurance,Stocks,Health Insurance,Car Loan,Income Tax,Fixed Deposits in India- Compare and apply online.

**Privacy Policy**

**IMPORTANT NOTICE**  
PLEASE READ OUR IMPORTANT TERMS AND CONDITIONS PRIOR TO READING THIS PRIVACY POLICY. PURSUANT TO WHICH, YOU ARE ADVISED TO PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. THE DEFINITIONS CONTAINED IN THE IMPORTANT TERMS AND CONDITIONS SHALL BE APPLICABLE HERE, UNLESS OVERTLY STATED TO THE CONTRARY. FURTHER, EACH TIME YOU ACCESS THIS SITE AND ANY PAGES THEREOF, YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND ALSO GRANT US UNCONDITIONAL RIGHTS TO USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM OUR SITE ACCORDING TO INDUSTRY PRACTICES AND CONSISTENT WITH THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY WHILE KEEPING SUCH USAGES WITHIN THE CONFINES OF APPLICABLE LAWS THAT ARE IN FORCE WITHIN THE REPUBLIC OF INDIA. 

**OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this Privacy Policy explaining our online information practices. To make this Privacy Policy easy to find, we make it available from all pages of our Site. 

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
This Privacy Policy applies to all bonafide information collected or submitted on our Site. We use the information you provide about yourself to, _inter alia_ , place cookies on your hard drive - this provides a more tailor-made experience during your use of our Site. 

Cookies are small pieces of information stored by us on your computer which enable us to identify your computer when you access our services or Site. We may use cookies to provide you with a convenient means of access, without needing your password. Also to protect the integrity of registered user names and passwords and to limit access to "paid for" services, if any. The third party companies who sell and provide advertisements to the Site and host our contacts database make use of cookies for the purpose of serving and targeting advertisements more effectively.

We may use this information, _inter alia_ , to get in touch with you (though any communication medium/platform now known or to be invented) when necessary and/or to provide the services requested by you and/or to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy. We may share this information with banks, factoring companies, etc. to proffer the best fit to your financial needs. We do not share this information with outside parties for the purpose of unrelated marketing which falls outside the purview of activities undertaken by our company. 

Finally, we never use or share any personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above under any circumstances whatsoever. 

**OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY**  
To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, _inter alia_ , we have put in place reasonably appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. While you can terminate your account at any time, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or termination of your account. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
We may change/alter/modify these terms and conditions at any time with or without notice. You unequivocally agree that your continued access or use this Site is clear testament to the fact that you have accepted all such changes/alterations/modifications _en toto_.
